Register of the Frederick L. Anderson papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Frederick L. Anderson papers
1917-1947
75054
Hoover Institution Archives
107 manuscript boxes, 12 oversize boxes, 17 oversize binders, 1 album box, 28 envelopes, 25 motion picture film reels (55.1 linear feet)
Correspondence, diaries, memoranda, reports, studies, notes, manuals, printed matter, motion picture film, photographs, and memorabilia relating primarily to Allied aerial bombardment strategy, tactics, and operations in Europe during World War II.
Anderson, Frederick L., 1905-1969.
Access
Collection is open for research.
Use copies of some motion picture film in this collection are available for immediate access. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, other films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1975.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1905 October 4 Born, Kingston, New York
1928 Graduated, U.S. Military Academy Commissioned 2nd Lieutenant
1929 Graduated from Kelly Field and Brooks Field Received wings Served in the Philippines, Hamilton Field, Lowry Field and Washington
1931 Transferred to bombardment aviation
1940 Operations officer, 7th Bombardment Group Selected to start first Bombardier's Instructor School
1941 Head of Bombardment Tactics Board Sent to England
1942 Deputy Director of Bombardment, Washington, D.C. Representative of General Arnold on bombardment matters in Northern Africa and England
1943 Commander, Fortress Wing in United Kingdom Promoted to Major General
1943-1944 Commanding General, VIII Bomber Command, England
1944-1945 Deputy Commanding General for Operations, U.S. Strategic Air Forces in Europe
1945-1947 Assistant Chief of Air Staff for Personnel
1947 Retired from the U.S. Air Force
1952-1953 Deputy United States Special Representative in Europe, with rank of ambassador
1969 March 2 Died, Houston, Texas
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, diaries, memoranda, reports, studies, notes, manuals, printed matter, motion picture film, photographs, and memorabilia relating primarily to Allied aerial bombardment strategy, tactics, and operations in Europe during World War II.
United States. Air Force--Officers.; United States. Army Air Forces.; World War, 1939-1945--Aerial operations.; United States. Army Air Forces. Air Force, 8th.; Bombing, Aerial.; Motion pictures.
- Biographical File, 1928-1946
  Scope and Contents note
  Flight records, itineraries, military orders, certificates, and clippings, relating primarily to Anderson's military career.
  - Clippings, Stockholm, Sweden, 1945 April (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Confidential orders, 1941 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Flight records
    - 1928-1939 (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - 1940-1947 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Itineraries, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Military orders, 1933-1941 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Special orders, 1942 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Trips, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Trips, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2: 1-2)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 2: 3)
- Speeches and Writings, 1943-1944
  Typescripts and photocopies of Anderson's speeches and writings, arranged chronologically.
  - "Airborne Radio Equipment," typescript, 1943 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Statement by Brig. Gen. Frederick L. Anderson, Commanding General, Eighth Air Force Bomber Command, mimeograph, 1943 August 17 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - "Psychological Aspects of United States Strategy,", 1955 November
    - Correspondence relating to (Box-folder 117: 1)
    - Drafts (Box-folder 117: 2-7)
    - Drafts (Box-folder 118: 1-3)
    - Printed copy (Box-folder 118: 4)
  - Miscellaneous typescripts of Anderson's speeches, comments and quotations of him by others, correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 2: 6)
- Diaries, 1943-1945
  Diaries and daily notes by Anderson, arranged chronologically.
  - 1943 February - August (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - 1943 September - 1944 February (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - 1944
    - March-July (Box-folder 2: 9)
    - September-December (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - 1945
    - January-February 2 (Box-folder 2: 11)
    - February 3 - April 17 (Box-folder 2: 12)
- Correspondence, 1938-1947
  Letters, memoranda, telegrams and enclosures, arranged chronologically or alphabetically by correspondent.
  - Index to letters and cables arranged by subject and date, 1944 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Chronological
    - 1941 (Box-folder 3: 2)
    - 1941-1942 (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - 1943-1945 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Outgoing memoranda, 1942
    - March-April (Box-folder 3: 5)
    - May-August (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Alphabetical
    - Aerosphere Aircraft Publications, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4: 1)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch Company, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 2)
    - Acheson, George R., 1947 (Box-folder 4: 3)
    - Acker, Brice, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 4)
    - Adamson, Hans C., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 5)
    - Agan, Arthur C., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 6)
    - Albert, John E., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 7)
    - Allard, Jack, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 8)
    - Allen, Julian, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 9)
    - Anderson, Clarence, 1942-1947 (Box-folder 4: 10)
    - Anderson, E. H., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 11)
    - Anderson, Mary Winn, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 12)
    - Anderson, Mrs. Fred, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 13)
    - Anderson, Samuel E., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 14)
    - Anderson, Travis, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 4: 15)
    - Andrews, W. G., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 16)
    - Anholt, Harry M., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 17)
    - Armstrong, Frank A., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 18)
    - Arnold, H. H., 1944-1947 (Box-folder 4: 19)
    - Atherton, Ray, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 20)
    - Atherton, Warren, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 21)
    - Atwood, Roy F., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 4: 22)
    - Bagby, Sarah, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 23)
    - Baker, Grenville, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 24)
    - Baker, Henry, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 25)
    - Baker, Ira, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 26)
    - Balchen, Berut, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 27)
    - Baldwin, Joseph C., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 28)
    - Bancroft, Thomas M., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 29)
    - Batson, Burnham, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 30)
    - Bazata, Arthur J., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 31)
    - Beach, Charles T., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 32)
    - Beal, Oscar, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 33)
    - Beard, Louis, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 34)
    - Beaverbrook, Lord, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 35)
    - Beckworth, Lindley, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 36)
    - Beebe, R. E., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 37)
    - Beeson, J. K., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 38)
    - Bell, Mortimer E., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 39)
    - Belzer, Martin, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 40)
    - Bender, Frank P., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 41)
    - Benjamin, Harold, undated (Box-folder 4: 42)
    - Bennett, J. M., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 43)
    - Bettle, Griscom, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 44)
    - Bevans, James, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 45)
    - Bevis, Robert, 1947 (Box-folder 4: 46)
    - Bibby, Henry L., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 47)
    - Bienfang, George R., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4: 48)
    - Bishop, C. W., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 49)
    - Bissell, Clayton, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 50)
    - Bitting, Kenneth, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 51)
    - Blakelock, Chester, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 52)
    - Boehling, Frank, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 53)
    - Bogert, James H., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 54)
    - Bolanes, Helen, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 55)
    - Bole, Thomas J., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 56)
    - Bolling Field Officers Club, 1942 (Box-folder 4: 57)
    - Bollinger, D. G., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 58)
    - Bonesteel, Robert W., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 59)
    - Bonevalie, Richard W., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 60)
    - Bonfils, F. W., 1942 (Box-folder 4: 61)
    - Bonney, Therese, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 62)
    - Bordelon, H. O., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 63)
    - Born, Charles, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 64)
    - Bottomley, Norman, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 65)
    - Bouscat, R., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 66)
    - Bowen, R. L., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 67)
    - Bowers, Walter A., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 68)
    - Bowman, H. W., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 69)
    - Bowman, Robert A., 1942 (Box-folder 4: 70)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Kingston, New York, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 71)
    - Boyd, Max, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 72)
    - Bradley, Follett, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 73)
    - Brady, William E., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 74)
    - Breehler, Vernon, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 75)
    - Brereton, L. H., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 76)
    - Brooks, John B., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 77)
    - Brotherton, W. J., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 78)
    - Brown, S. Perry, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 79)
    - Brownell, George A., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 80)
    - Brownfield, Ralph O., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 81)
    - Brummel, D. B., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 82)
    - Bruno, Harry, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 83)
    - Bruno, Louis, undated (Box-folder 4: 84)
    - Buck, C. Douglass, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4: 85)
    - Buckingham, John, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 86)
    - Buffett, Howard, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 87)
    - Bufton, Sydney, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 88)
    - Bulger, Joseph, 1945 (Box-folder 4: 89)
    - Burns, James F., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 90)
    - Burns, Robert W., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 91)
    - Burt, W. R., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 92)
    - Burton, Alexander T., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 93)
    - Buseck, Lawrence A., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 94)
    - Byrd, D. Harold, 1946 (Box-folder 4: 95)
    - Byrne, William T., 1946 (Box-folder 4: 96)
    - Byrnes, John W., 1945 (Box-folder 4: 97)
    - Cahill, James R., 1942 (Box-folder 5: 1)
    - Callahan, Larry, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5: 2)
    - Campbell, H. L., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 3)
    - Campbell, John, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 4)
    - Campbell, Milt, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 5)
    - Campbell, Thomas D., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 6)
    - Canaday, Ward M., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 7)
    - Candee, R. C., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 8)
    - Cannon, John K., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 9)
    - Carl, 1938 (Box-folder 5: 10)
    - Carolin, Norbert, 1942 (Box-folder 5: 11)
    - Carrel, Granville, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 5: 12)
    - Carter, Amon, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5: 13)
    - Cartwright, William, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 14)
    - Case, R. W., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 15)
    - Casey, Samuel B., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 16)
    - Castle, Benjamin F., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 17)
    - Chennault, Claire L., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 18)
    - Christine, Frederick F., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 19)
    - Churchill, Winston, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 20)
    - Clapp, Charles, 1942 (Box-folder 5: 21)
    - Clarke, Frank W., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 5: 22)
    - Clason, Congressman, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 23)
    - Clay, Walter J., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 24)
    - Cochran, Jacqueline, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 25)
    - Cocreham, Roland, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 26)
    - Coleman, William W., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 27)
    - Colmery, Harry W., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 28)
    - Colyer, Douglas, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5: 29)
    - Cook, Everett, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 5: 30)
    - Cooper, Merian, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 5: 31)
    - Corley, W. B., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 32)
    - Corman, Margaret L., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5: 33)
    - Corregan, Robert H., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 34)
    - Coughlan, Robert, 1945 (Box-folder 5: 35)
    - Cox, Albert L., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 36)
    - Craig, Howard A., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 37)
    - Cramer, Janet, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 38)
    - Craver, Robert V., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 39)
    - Crawford, F. C., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 40)
    - Crowe, Samuel J., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 41)
    - Curtis, Edward P., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 5: 42)
    - Curtis, W. A., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 43)
    - Danforth, W. J., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 44)
    - Darcy, Thomas C., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 45)
    - Davidson, G. Noble, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 46)
    - Davis, Chester, 1945 (Box-folder 5: 47)
    - Davis, K. S., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 48)
    - Davison, F. Trubee, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 49)
    - Dennis, Mr., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 50)
    - Dewey, W. E., 1947 (Box-folder 5: 51)
    - Dilley, George E., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 52)
    - Dillon, John J., 1945 (Box-folder 5: 53)
    - D'Olier, Franklin, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 54)
    - Donald-Donaldson, James, 1945 (Box-folder 5: 55)
    - Donnaruma, Walter, 1945 (Box-folder 5: 56)
    - Doolittle, James H., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 5: 57)
    - Douglas, Hal, 1946 (Box-folder 5: 58)
    - Douglas Aircraft Company, 1947 (Box-folder 5: 59)
    - Douglass, Kingman, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5: 60)
    - Douglass, Robert W., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 61)
    - Drake, Francis, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 5: 62)
    - Dumm, Clarence, 1945 (Box-folder 5: 63)
    - Dunn, W. W., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 64)
    - Durham, Robert C., 1946 (Box-folder 5: 65)
    - Dwyer, Martin, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5: 66)
    - Eaker, Ira C., 1943-1947 (Box-folder 6: 1)
    - Earle, Edward, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 6: 2)
    - Earle, Ralph, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 3)
    - Eble, Ferdinand, 1945 (Box-folder 6: 4)
    - Echols, Oliver, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 5)
    - Edelmuth, William F., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 6)
    - Edmonson, John P., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 7)
    - Edwards, W. P. N., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 8)
    - Egan, John W., 1942 (Box-folder 6: 9)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 10)
    - Elliott, A. W., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 11)
    - Elson, Robert T., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 12)
    - Elvins, Richard E., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 13)
    - Emanuel, Victor, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 14)
    - Engler, Howard, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 15)
    - Engler, Paul, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 16)
    - Ent, Uzal, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6: 17)
    - Erdel, Milton W., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 18)
    - Ervin, Gil, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 19)
    - Etherington, John S., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 20)
    - Eubank, Eugene L., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 6: 21)
    - Everest, F. F., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 22)
    - Everett, Dewey E., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 23)
    - Fairchild, Muir S., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6: 24)
    - Farnsworth, Sid W., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 25)
    - Faversham, William, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 26)
    - Fay, Dudley, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6: 27)
    - Fechet, James E., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 28)
    - Fellowes, William, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 29)
    - Fellows, Robert, 1942 (Box-folder 6: 30)
    - Fickel, J. E., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 31)
    - Fischer, Marion, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 32)
    - Fisher, William P., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 33)
    - Fitch, Willis, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 34)
    - Fitzgerald, Donald, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 35)
    - Fix, George J., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 36)
    - Flanagan, Father (Boys Town), 1942, 1945 (Box-folder 6: 37)
    - Fleer, Henry, 1945 (Box-folder 6: 38)
    - Fleming, Raymond H., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 39)
    - Flood, Hope, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 40)
    - Forbes, Arthur, 1945 (Box-folder 6: 41)
    - Ford, Corey, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 42)
    - Foster, J. W. S., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 43)
    - Foster, John, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 44)
    - Frazer, Charles D., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6: 45)
    - Fritz, L. G., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 46)
    - Fritzsche, Carl F., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 47)
    - Frost, Lt., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 48)
    - Fulbright, J. W., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 49)
    - Gaffney, Dale V., 1938, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 50)
    - Gage, Charles, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 51)
    - Gailhouse, C. B., 1945 (Box-folder 6: 52)
    - Gardner, B. B., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6: 53)
    - Gardner, Grandison, 1942 (Box-folder 6: 54)
    - Gardner, James E., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 55)
    - Garland, William M., 1942 (Box-folder 6: 56)
    - Gentile, Don, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 57)
    - George, Harold L., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 6: 58)
    - Geyer, Ken E., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 59)
    - Gibson, Myrtle, 1942 (Box-folder 6: 60)
    - Gilbert, E. C., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 61)
    - Gilchrist, Kenneth, 1942 (Box-folder 6: 62)
    - Gilchrist, Gibb, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 63)
    - Giles, B. F., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 64)
    - Gill, Mary E., 1946 (Box-folder 6: 65)
    - Goddard, R. V., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 6: 66)
    - Goetz, M. Karl, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 67)
    - Golden, S. B., 1938 (Box-folder 6: 68)
    - Goodrich, Charles G., 1942 (Box-folder 6: 69)
    - Greig, Louis, 1945 (Box-folder 6: 70)
    - Griffith, John, 1947 (Box-folder 6: 71)
    - Griswold, Francis H., 1947 (Box-folder 6: 72)
    - Gross, Mildred, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 6: 73)
    - Gross, Robert, 1942 (Box-folder 6: 74)
    - Guest, Raymond, 1946 (Box-folder 6: 75)
    - Gurney, Chan, (?), 1947 (Box-folder 6: 76)
    - Hadden, John A., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 1)
    - Hagen, Harold C., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 2)
    - Hager, Dilworth, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 3)
    - Hagglof, Brita, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 4)
    - Haines, William W., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 7: 5)
    - Hale, Willis, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 6)
    - Hall, William, 1947 (Box-folder 7: 7)
    - Hamlin, Walter, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 8)
    - Handy, R. B., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 9)
    - Hanner, Charles K., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 10)
    - Harbold, Norris B., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 11)
    - Harlan, John M., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 12)
    - Harmon, Hubert, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 7: 13)
    - Harriman, Averell, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7: 14)
    - Harriman, E. Roland, 1947 (Box-folder 7: 15)
    - Harrington, Claude, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 16)
    - Harris, Arthur, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 17)
    - Harris, Harold R., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 18)
    - Hastings, K. L., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 19)
    - Hayes, Rex P., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 20)
    - Haynes, C. V., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 21)
    - Haynes, J., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 22)
    - Hazlehurst, Dorr, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 23)
    - Hearst, William, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7: 24)
    - Hedrick, William F., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 25)
    - Henderson, Hope, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 26)
    - Henderson, Walter, 1947 (Box-folder 7: 27)
    - Henry, Draper F., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 28)
    - Henschel, Harry D., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 29)
    - Hensley, William H., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7: 30)
    - Hernden, T. B., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 31)
    - Hertel, F. S., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 32)
    - Higgins, G. J., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 33)
    - Higgs, James H., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 34)
    - Hill, Alden T., 1942 (Box-folder 7: 35)
    - Hill, Lon C., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 36)
    - Hilton, Frank R., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 37)
    - Hinshaw, Carl, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 38)
    - Hoag, Earl, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 39)
    - Hockman, David A., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 40)
    - Hodges, James P., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 41)
    - Holderman, E. M., (?), 1945 (Box-folder 7: 42)
    - Holliers, James P., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 43)
    - Holman, Charles W., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 44)
    - Hoover, Edwin H., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 45)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 46)
    - Hope, William S., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7: 47)
    - Hopkins, Frederick, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 48)
    - Hopper, Bruce C., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7: 49)
    - Hopwood, Lloyd P., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 50)
    - Hornsby, Aubrey, 1947 (Box-folder 7: 51)
    - Hotel Fado, 1942 (Box-folder 7: 52)
    - Hover, Blanche, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 53)
    - Howard, Roy, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7: 54)
    - Howe, Deering, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 55)
    - Hoyt, Kendall, 1947 (Box-folder 7: 56)
    - Hoyt, Palmer, 1947 (Box-folder 7: 57)
    - Huau, Joseph, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 58)
    - Huff, S. P., 1942, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 59)
    - Hughes, Louis R., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 60)
    - Hughes, Richard D., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7: 61)
    - Hull, H. B., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 62)
    - Hummel, Fred, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 63)
    - Hunt, C. T., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 64)
    - Hunter, Frank D., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 65)
    - Ireland, Ray, 1947 (Box-folder 7: 66)
    - Jackson, William H., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 67)
    - Jamieson, Edward, 1945 (Box-folder 7: 68)
    - Jarmon, R. E., 1942 (Box-folder 7: 69)
    - Jarvis, Clara L., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 70)
    - Jenkins, John G., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 71)
    - Johnson, Davenport, 1938 (Box-folder 7: 72)
    - Johnson, Earle, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7: 73)
    - Johnson, Harry A., 1942 (Box-folder 7: 74)
    - Johnson, Herschel, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7: 75)
    - Johnson, Leon W., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 76)
    - Johnson, Leroy, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 7: 77)
    - Johnson, Louis A., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 78)
    - Johnston, Gerald G., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 7: 79)
    - Johnston, W. S., 1947 (Box-folder 7: 80)
    - Jolly, Edith D., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 81)
    - Jones, Curran L., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 82)
    - Jones, George W., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7: 83)
    - Jones, Homer, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 7: 84)
    - Jones, R. O., 1942 (Box-folder 7: 85)
    - Jones, Richard, 1946 (Box-folder 7: 86)
    - Jones, Robert C., 1945 (Box-folder 7: 87)
    - Jouett, John H., 1946 (Box-folder 7: 88)
    - Kachigin, Howard J., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 1)
    - Kantor, Mackinlay, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8: 2)
    - Karn, Colonel, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 3)
    - Kavanagh, E. C., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 4)
    - Kearns, Edward P., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 5)
    - Keighley, William, (?), 1945 (Box-folder 8: 6)
    - Kelley, Howard A., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 7)
    - Kelley, Lois, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 8)
    - Kelly, Delmer, 1942 (Box-folder 8: 9)
    - Kelly, James J., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 10)
    - Kelly, Joseph, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 11)
    - Keltner, K. W., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 12)
    - Kennedy, Thomas H., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 13)
    - Kenney, George C., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8: 14)
    - Kenney, Lawrence A., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 15)
    - Kenny, John P., 1941-1942 (Box-folder 8: 16)
    - Kepner, William E., 1944-1947 (Box-folder 8: 17)
    - Kerl, Mrs. Thomas T., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 18)
    - Kern, Edward P., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8: 19)
    - Kessler, Alfred A., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8: 20)
    - Ketchum, Omar, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 21)
    - Kight, Richard T., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 22)
    - Kimball, Lindsley, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 23)
    - King, Henry, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 24)
    - Kingston, New York, Citizens of, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 25)
    - Kinzie, George F., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 8: 26)
    - Kirkpatrick, Helen P., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 27)
    - Kissner, A. W., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 8: 28)
    - Klette, Immanuel J., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 29)
    - Kline, Allen B., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 30)
    - Knerr, Hugh, 1942, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 31)
    - Knopf, Blanche, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 32)
    - Koon, R. E., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 33)
    - Krans, Walter F., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 34)
    - Kriendler, Maxwell A., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 35)
    - Kring, Kay, 1947 (Box-folder 8: 36)
    - Kring, Mrs. C. U., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 37)
    - Kuter, Laurence, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 8: 38)
    - Lackie, Robert, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 39)
    - Laffon, Marcel, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 8: 40)
    - Laney, Ben T., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 41)
    - Laughry, James D., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 42)
    - Lauro, Frank, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 8: 43)
    - Law, H. L., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 8: 44)
    - Lawson, Lawrence A., 1942 (Box-folder 8: 45)
    - Lay, Beirne, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 46)
    - Leach, W. Barton, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 8: 47)
    - Lear, Lester, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 48)
    - Lee, Ellis A., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 49)
    - Lee, Robert M., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 50)
    - Lefevre, Jay, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 51)
    - Leflar, Robert A., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 52)
    - Legg, Richard, 1947 (Box-folder 8: 53)
    - Lehman, Robert, 1947 (Box-folder 8: 54)
    - Leitner, Charles, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 55)
    - LeMay, Curtis, 1945 (Box-folder 8: 56)
    - Leo, Stephen, 1947 (Box-folder 8: 57)
    - Leonard, Marston, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 58)
    - Lessig, C. B., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8: 59)
    - Lesueur, Larry, 1947 (Box-folder 8: 60)
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 61)
    - Lewis, William C., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 62)